{
  "questions": [
    {
      "question": "Hardware RAID Level 0: (Select all that apply)",
      "options": [
        "Requires a minimum of 2 drives to implement",
        "Is also known as disk striping",
        "Decreases reliability (failure of any disk in the array results in the loss of all data in the array)",
        "Is also referred to as disk mirroring",
        "Offers less volume capacity in comparison to RAID 1",
        "Requires at least 3 drives to implement",
        "Is suitable for systems where performance has higher priority than fault tolerance",
        "Offers improved reliability by creating identical data sets on each drive (failure of one drive does not destroy the array as each drive contains identical copy of the data)"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Requires a minimum of 2 drives to implement",
        "Is also known as disk striping",
        "Decreases reliability (failure of any disk in the array results in the loss of all data in the array)",
        "Is suitable for systems where performance has higher priority than fault tolerance"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Hardware RAID Level 1: (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Requires at least 2 drives to implement",
        "Is also known as disk striping",
        "Offers improved performance in comparison to RAID 0",
        "Requires at least 3 drives to implement",
        "Offers improved reliability by creating identical data sets on each drive (failure of one drive does not destroy the array as each drive contains identical copy of the data)",
        "Is also referred to as disk mirroring"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Requires at least 2 drives to implement",
        "Offers improved reliability by creating identical data sets on each drive (failure of one drive does not destroy the array as each drive contains identical copy of the data)",
        "Is also referred to as disk mirroring"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Hardware RAID Level 5: (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Requires at least 2 drives to implement",
        "Continues to operate in case of failure of more than 1 drive",
        "Is also known as disk striping with double parity",
        "Requires at least 3 drives to implement",
        "Offers increased performance and fault tolerance (single drive failure does not destroy the array and lost data can be re-created by the remaining drives)",
        "Requires at least 4 drives to implement",
        "Is also known as disk striping with parity"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Requires at least 3 drives to implement",
        "Offers increased performance and fault tolerance (single drive failure does not destroy the array and lost data can be re-created by the remaining drives)",
        "Is also known as disk striping with parity"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Hardware RAID Level 6: (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Is also known as disk striping with parity",
        "Requires at least 4 drives to implement",
        "Offers increased performance and fault tolerance (failure of up to 2 drives does not destroy the array and lost data can be re-created by the remaining drives)",
        "Requires at least 3 drives to implement",
        "Is also known as disk striping with double parity",
        "Continues to operate in case of failure of more than 2 drives",
        "Requires at least 5 drives to implement"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Requires at least 4 drives to implement",
        "Offers increased performance and fault tolerance (failure of up to 2 drives does not destroy the array and lost data can be re-created by the remaining drives)",
        "Is also known as disk striping with double parity"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Hardware RAID Level 10 (a.k.a. RAID 1+0): (Select 3 answers)",
      "options": [
        "Requires a minimum of 4 drives to implement",
        "Is referred to as stripe of mirrors, i.e., a combination of RAID 1 (disk mirroring) and RAID 0 (disk striping)",
        "Requires a minimum of 5 drives to implement",
        "Offers increased performance and fault tolerance (failure of one drive in each mirrored pair of disk drives does not destroy the array)",
        "Requires a minimum of 3 drives to implement",
        "Continues to operate in case of failure of more than 2 drives",
        "Is referred to as stripe of mirrors, i.e., a combination of RAID 1 (disk striping) and RAID 0 (disk mirroring)"
      ],
      "correct_answers": [
        "Requires a minimum of 4 drives to implement",
        "Is referred to as stripe of mirrors, i.e., a combination of RAID 1 (disk mirroring) and RAID 0 (disk striping)",
        "Offers increased performance and fault tolerance (failure of one drive in each mirrored pair of disk drives does not destroy the array)"
      ]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following RAID levels does not offer fault tolerance?",
      "options": ["RAID 6", "RAID 10", "RAID 5", "RAID 0", "RAID 1"],
      "correct_answers": ["RAID 0"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to the primary function of load balancing?",
      "options": [
        "Maintains identical copies of data across multiple servers to enhance data availability and reliability",
        "Distributes workload across multiple servers for improved performance",
        "Groups servers together to provide high availability and fault tolerance",
        "Distributes content geographically across multiple servers to improve performance, reduce latency, and handle high volumes of traffic"
      ],
      "correct_answers": ["Distributes workload across multiple servers for improved performance"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following is the primary function of clustering?",
      "options": [
        "Distributes content geographically across multiple servers to improve performance, reduce latency, and handle high volumes of traffic",
        "Groups servers together to provide high availability and fault tolerance",
        "Maintains identical copies of data across multiple servers to enhance data availability and reliability",
        "Distributes workload across multiple servers for improved performance"
      ],
      "correct_answers": ["Groups servers together to provide high availability and fault tolerance"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the terms listed below refers to a duplicate of the original site, with fully operational computer systems as well as near-complete backups of user data?",
      "options": ["Hot site", "Warm site", "Cold site", "Mobile site"],
      "correct_answers": ["Hot site"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms refers to an alternate site that provides some pre-installed hardware and software and might have partial data backups, but it is not fully operational and requires additional configuration before use?",
      "options": ["Cold site", "Hot site", "Mirror site", "Warm site"],
      "correct_answers": ["Warm site"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A disaster recovery facility that provides only the physical space for recovery operations is known as:",
      "options": ["Hot site", "Warm site", "Cold site", "Mirror site"],
      "correct_answers": ["Cold site"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which alternate site is the least expensive to implement?",
      "options": ["Cold site", "Mirror site", "Warm site", "Hot site"],
      "correct_answers": ["Cold site"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which alternate site allows for the fastest disaster recovery?",
      "options": ["Cold site", "Hot site", "Mobile site", "Warm site"],
      "correct_answers": ["Hot site"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a U.S. government initiative that provides a set of procedures and plans that an organization can implement to ensure continued performance of its essential functions during unexpected events?",
      "options": ["SLA", "COOP", "RPO", "BIA"],
      "correct_answers": ["COOP"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a simulated scenario conducted in a controlled environment, typically involving discussions and planning around hypothetical security incidents?",
      "options": ["Tabletop exercise", "Sandboxing", "Threat hunting", "Security awareness training"],
      "correct_answers": ["Tabletop exercise"]
    },
    {
      "question": "The process of switching to a redundant or standby system upon detecting a disruption in the primary system is called:",
      "options": ["Fail over", "Multipath I/O", "Load balancing", "Parallel processing"],
      "correct_answers": ["Fail over"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following answers refers to a more realistic scenario that tests cybersecurity incident response by mimicking actual attacks?",
      "options": ["Fingerprinting", "Simulation", "Threat hunting", "Tabletop exercise"],
      "correct_answers": ["Simulation"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the solutions listed below provides redundancy and fault tolerance by dividing tasks into smaller subtasks and distributing them across multiple systems to be executed simultaneously?",
      "options": ["Load balancing", "Multitasking", "Clustering", "Parallel processing"],
      "correct_answers": ["Parallel processing"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A file-based representation of the state of a virtual machine at a given point in time is referred to as:",
      "options": ["Restore point", "Shadow copy", "Snapshot", "System image"],
      "correct_answers": ["Snapshot"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What type of backups are commonly used with virtual machines?",
      "options": ["Incremental backups", "Snapshot backups", "Tape backups", "Differential backups"],
      "correct_answers": ["Snapshot backups"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following terms refers to a backup strategy that relies on creating and maintaining copies of data in real-time or near real-time on a separate system?",
      "options": ["Mirroring", "Virtualization", "Journaling", "Replication"],
      "correct_answers": ["Replication"]
    },
    {
      "question": "A technique that allows to recover changes that occurred since the last backup in the event of a system crash is known as:",
      "options": ["Replication", "Journaling", "Virtualization", "Mirroring"],
      "correct_answers": ["Journaling"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the answers listed below refers to a device designed to supply (and monitor the quality of) electric power to multiple outlets?",
      "options": ["PSU", "MDF", "PDU", "IDF"],
      "correct_answers": ["PDU"]
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the name of a device that can provide short-term emergency power during an unexpected main power source outage?",
      "options": ["UPS", "PoE", "SVC", "PSU"],
      "correct_answers": ["UPS"]
    },
    {
      "question": "Which of the following power redundancy solutions would be best suited for providing long-term emergency power during an unexpected main power source outage?",
      "options": ["Dual-power supply", "Standby UPS", "Backup generator", "Managed PDU"],
      "correct_answers": ["Backup generator"]
    }
  ]
}